(Leonard:)Thanks, yeah.
Sure.
(Bernadette:)Let me help you.
(Howard:)Nice to see that the gals
are getting along.
"Gals"?
(Leonard:)Who are you, Fred Flintstone?
(Penny:)This trip to India
sounds fun.
(Priya:)Yeah, I think it will be.
(Bernadette:)Are you concerned your parents
might not approve of Leonard?
(Priya:)A little.
(Priya:)They're very old-fashioned.
(Bernadette:)Well, I wouldn't
worry about it.
(Bernadette:)It's not like you guys
are getting engaged, right?
(Priya:)Oh, God, no.
We're not there yet.
(Bernadette:)Not engaged.
Very interesting.
(Bernadette:)I have to tinkle.
(Priya:)You've been in there
a lot tonight. Are you okay?
(Sheldon:)Yes.
Are you writing a book?
(Priya:)Why are you getting upset?
(Bernadette:)I'm not upset.
Maybe you're upset.
(Priya:)What's up with you?
(Amy:)Bernadette?
(Bernadette:)I can't do this anymore!
(Bernadette:)I'm a good girl!